import { Question } from "../components/MovieQuiz";

export const squidData: Question[] = [
  {
    question: "What is the main premise of 'Squid Game'?",
    options: [
      "A deadly survival game",
      "A high-stakes poker game",
      "A reality TV competition",
      "A corporate takeover",
    ],
    answer: "A deadly survival game",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the character who organizes the games?",
    options: ["The Front Man", "The Host", "The Master", "The Game Maker"],
    answer: "The Front Man",
  },
  {
    question: "Which game is played first in the series?",
    options: ["Red Light, Green Light", "Tug of War", "Marbles", "Squid Game"],
    answer: "Red Light, Green Light",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the primary motivation for the characters to participate in the games?",
    options: [
      "Winning a large cash prize",
      "Gaining fame",
      "Avoiding criminal charges",
      "Seeking revenge",
    ],
    answer: "Winning a large cash prize",
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the main protagonist of the series?",
    options: ["Seong Gi-hun", "Cho Sang-woo", "Kang Sae-byeok", "Hwang Jun-ho"],
    answer: "Seong Gi-hun",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the character who is a North Korean defector and participates in the games?",
    options: ["Kang Sae-byeok", "Oh Il-nam", "Jang Deok-su", "Ji-yeong"],
    answer: "Kang Sae-byeok",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What game do players have to play in the second round of the competition?",
    options: ["Honeycomb", "Marbles", "Tug of War", "Glass Bridge"],
    answer: "Honeycomb",
  },
  {
    question: "What role does the character Oh Il-nam play in the series?",
    options: ["A player", "A game designer", "A guard", "A sponsor"],
    answer: "A player",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the organization that runs the deadly games?",
    options: [
      "The Game Masters",
      "The Organizers",
      "The VIPs",
      "The Front Man",
    ],
    answer: "The VIPs",
  },
  {
    question: "How does Seong Gi-hun change by the end of the series?",
    options: [
      "He becomes a wealthy businessman",
      "He seeks revenge on the organizers",
      "He becomes a player in the games",
      "He becomes an advocate for the games' victims",
    ],
    answer: "He becomes an advocate for the games' victims",
  },
];
